

CONTACT



+234-706-488-6392



 ${\bf MIchael Oluwayemi 11@gmail.com}$



https://github.com/nerdyxg



5, Oke-Ayo, Akodu, Ariibi, Apete, Ibadan.

SKILLS

- Team Work
- Time Management
- Leadership
- Verbal & Written

Communication

- Teaching and Learning
- Coding {Python, HTML5, CSS3,
 JavaScript, JQuery, BS5, Node.js}
- Graphic Designing
- Drawing and Animating

LANGUAGE

- English
- Yoruba

OLATUNJI MICHAEL OLUWAYEMI

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a website developer with 3+ years of experience in the art and science of creating astonishing website projects with great UI/UX.

I am a creative, sharp-minded person with leadership & coaching skills. Strong time-management skills and work ethic. Revenue- and results-driven.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teacher

March 2018 - April 2020.

Effectively managed a class of 150 high school students in 3 different high schools. Oversaw their training in the discipline of Computer Science, Mathematics, English Language, Physics, Biology, Chemistry, Information Technology and some other subjects. Some of my students are now doing well in the Institution of their choice, while the others are flourishing in their high school journey.

Graphic Designer

September 2021 - March 2022.

Worked as an intern in a printing press company. There I experienced what it truly means to be a graphic designer. I got familiarized myself with some modern graphic editing applications, and I also handled and managed some projects.

Web Developer

January 2018 - .January 2020

Worked as a part-time front-end developer at a tech company for about two years, before I became a free-lancer.

EDUCATION

The University of Ibadan 2019 - 2023

BSC / Bachelor of Science || Computer Science